{"sid": "H87U3WJ4ZI0S_main", "calc_equals_delay": 5, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 336181, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 336182, "question": "24+516", "correct_answer": 540, "events": [["submit", 343019]], "time_left_end": "294", "answered_time": 343019, "user_answer": "540", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "294", "question_time_start": 343019, "question": "4+24+17", "correct_answer": 45, "events": [["submit", 348069]], "time_left_end": "289", "answered_time": 348069, "user_answer": "45", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "289", "question_time_start": 348069, "question": "78+37+23+47", "correct_answer": 185, "events": [["submit", 359542]], "time_left_end": "277", "answered_time": 359542, "user_answer": "185", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "277", "question_time_start": 359542, "question": "4+3+6+13", "correct_answer": 26, "events": [["submit", 364925]], "time_left_end": "272", "answered_time": 364925, "user_answer": "26", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "272", "question_time_start": 364925, "question": "6+7+7+43", "correct_answer": 63, "events": [["submit", 369513]], "time_left_end": "267", "answered_time": 369513, "user_answer": "63", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "267", "question_time_start": 369513, "question": "34+873", "correct_answer": 907, "events": [["submit", 378117]], "time_left_end": "259", "answered_time": 378117, "user_answer": "907", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "259", "question_time_start": 378117, "question": "8+98+77", "correct_answer": 183, "events": [["submit", 388706]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 388706, "user_answer": "183", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 388707, "question": "63+13", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 391429]], "time_left_end": "245", "answered_time": 391429, "user_answer": "76", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "245", "question_time_start": 391429, "question": "7+68+83", "correct_answer": 158, "events": [["submit", 400523]], "time_left_end": "236", "answered_time": 400523, "user_answer": "155", "user_correct": "False", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "236", "question_time_start": 400523, "question": "64+86", "correct_answer": 150, "events": [["submit", 405861]], "time_left_end": "231", "answered_time": 405861, "user_answer": "150", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 405861, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "231", "question_time_start": 405861, "question": "3+19+69", "correct_answer": 91, "events": [["submit", 416082]], "time_left_end": "221", "answered_time": 416082, "user_answer": "91", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "221", "question_time_start": 416083, "question": "6+18+74", "correct_answer": 98, "events": [["submit", 420337]], "time_left_end": "216", "answered_time": 420337, "user_answer": "98", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "216", "question_time_start": 420338, "question": "76+587", "correct_answer": 663, "events": [["submit", 429160]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 429160, "user_answer": "663", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 429160, "question": "4+47+36", "correct_answer": 87, "events": [["submit", 433361]], "time_left_end": "203", "answered_time": 433361, "user_answer": "87", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "203", "question_time_start": 433361, "question": "57+16+27+86", "correct_answer": 186, "events": [["submit", 447783]], "time_left_end": "189", "answered_time": 447783, "user_answer": "176", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "189", "question_time_start": 447783, "question": "8+9+4+59", "correct_answer": 80, "events": [["submit", 455424]], "time_left_end": "181", "answered_time": 455424, "user_answer": "80", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "181", "question_time_start": 455424, "question": "27+49", "correct_answer": 76, "events": [["submit", 460249]], "time_left_end": "176", "answered_time": 460249, "user_answer": "73", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "176", "question_time_start": 460249, "question": "86+516", "correct_answer": 602, "events": [["submit", 469798]], "time_left_end": "167", "answered_time": 469798, "user_answer": "602", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "167", "question_time_start": 469798, "question": "7+3+7+93", "correct_answer": 110, "events": [["submit", 474323]], "time_left_end": "162", "answered_time": 474323, "user_answer": "110", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "162", "question_time_start": 474323, "question": "99+58", "correct_answer": 157, "events": [["submit", 482881]], "time_left_end": "154", "answered_time": 482881, "user_answer": "157", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 482881, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "154", "question_time_start": 482881, "question": "3+7+6+86", "correct_answer": 102, "events": [["submit", 488299]], "time_left_end": "148", "answered_time": 488299, "user_answer": "102", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "148", "question_time_start": 488299, "question": "6+78+34", "correct_answer": 118, "events": [["submit", 495213]], "time_left_end": "141", "answered_time": 495213, "user_answer": "118", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "141", "question_time_start": 495213, "question": "88+957", "correct_answer": 1045, "events": [["submit", 501498]], "time_left_end": "135", "answered_time": 501498, "user_answer": "1085", "user_correct": "False", "score": "15"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "135", "question_time_start": 501498, "question": "4+73+18", "correct_answer": 95, "events": [["submit", 510630]], "time_left_end": "126", "answered_time": 510630, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "126", "question_time_start": 510630, "question": "84+54+54+64", "correct_answer": 256, "events": [["calc_1", 520083], ["calc_3", 520563], ["calc_8", 521175], ["calc_+", 521769], ["calc_1", 522515], ["calc_1", 522689], ["calc_8", 523389], ["calc_=", 524025], ["submit", 532024]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "105", "answered_time": 532024, "user_answer": "256", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "105", "question_time_start": 532024, "question": "76+13", "correct_answer": 89, "events": [["submit", 535689]], "time_left_end": "101", "answered_time": 535689, "user_answer": "89", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "101", "question_time_start": 535690, "question": "9+77+86", "correct_answer": 172, "events": [["submit", 545683]], "time_left_end": "91", "answered_time": 545683, "user_answer": "172", "user_correct": "True", "score": "19"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "91", "question_time_start": 545683, "question": "84+827", "correct_answer": 911, "events": [["submit", 560570]], "time_left_end": "76", "answered_time": 560570, "user_answer": "911", "user_correct": "True", "score": "20"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "76", "question_time_start": 560570, "question": "8+3+6+33", "correct_answer": 50, "events": [["submit", 566630]], "time_left_end": "70", "answered_time": 566630, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "True", "score": "21"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "70", "question_time_start": 566630, "question": "99+17", "correct_answer": 116, "events": [["submit", 571547]], "time_left_end": "65", "answered_time": 571547, "user_answer": "116", "user_correct": "True", "score": "22"}}}, "block_3": {"mean_level": 8, "start_time": 571547, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "65", "question_time_start": 571547, "question": "43+816", "correct_answer": 859, "events": [["submit", 576910]], "time_left_end": "60", "answered_time": 576910, "user_answer": "859", "user_correct": "True", "score": "23"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "60", "question_time_start": 576910, "question": "9+3+9+23", "correct_answer": 44, "events": [["submit", 582205]], "time_left_end": "54", "answered_time": 582205, "user_answer": "44", "user_correct": "True", "score": "24"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "54", "question_time_start": 582206, "question": "4+57+77", "correct_answer": 138, "events": [["submit", 595818]], "time_left_end": "41", "answered_time": 595818, "user_answer": "138", "user_correct": "True", "score": "25"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "41", "question_time_start": 595818, "question": "63+723", "correct_answer": 786, "events": [["submit", 601453]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 601453, "user_answer": "786", "user_correct": "True", "score": "26"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 601453, "question": "6+87+78", "correct_answer": 171, "events": [["submit", 615485]], "time_left_end": "21", "answered_time": 615485, "user_answer": "171", "user_correct": "True", "score": "27"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "21", "question_time_start": 615485, "question": "6+14+63", "correct_answer": 83, "events": [["submit", 618967]], "time_left_end": "18", "answered_time": 618967, "user_answer": "83", "user_correct": "True", "score": "28"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "18", "question_time_start": 618967, "question": "7+7+7+39", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 623326]], "time_left_end": "13", "answered_time": 623326, "user_answer": "50", "user_correct": "False", "score": "27"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "13", "question_time_start": 623327, "question": "78+58+96+59", "correct_answer": 291, "events": []}}}}}